We're going to start with simply opening a blank spreadsheet.
首先打开一个空的电子表格
If you've reviewed the Getting Started Guide,
如果你已经阅读了入门指南
this should be straightforward.
就会发现操作很简单
In this example, I've opened a new Excel spreadsheet by
在此示例中 我打开新的 Excel 电子表格的操作为
clicking on File, New, Blank spreadsheet.
依次点击 文件 &gt; 新建 &gt; 电子表格
The spreadsheet has a series of columns with letter labels A,
电子表格有一系列的列
B, C, and so on.
分别标为 A B C 等等
If you go past Z, they become AA,
如果大于 Z 则变成 AA
AB, AC, and continue in that pattern.
AB AC 并继续这一模式
Meanwhile, rows are labeled numerically 1,2,3, and so on.
此外 行用数字 1 2 3 等标记
These boxes are called cells.
这些方框称为单元格
And each one has an address.
每个单元格都有一个地址
The address of this cell, for example,
例如这个单元格的地址是 A1
is A1, and this one is E8.
这个是 E8
You can see that the label boxes are grayed in the E and the 8.
可以看出标记方框 E 和 8 变成了灰色
In spreadsheets, you can also have multiple sheets.
电子表格还可以有多个工作表 (sheet)
Here is the add sheets button.
这是添加工作表按钮
I can add sheets easily and even rename them to something more useful.
我可以轻松地添加工作表 甚至重命名为有意义的名称
At first, we're just going to work on one sheet but keep in mind that
一开始我们只处理一个工作表 但是要记住
the sheet or tab name will become part of
当我们创建了多个工作表时 工作表或标签页的名称
the cell address when we work with multiple sheets.
将变成单元格地址的一部分
The formula bar is your window into a selected cell.
公式栏是选定单元格的窗口
If you start typing into a cell,
如果开始在单元格中输入内容
you can see your typing appear in the formula bar.
会看到输入的内容出现在了公式栏里
Alternatively, you could select the cell and type directly into the formula bar.
也可以选择单元格并直接在公式栏里输入内容
Sometimes, you'll be entering a formula as I have here.
有时候 你会像我这样输入一个公式
I'm adding two cells together by entering an equal sign and
我通过输入等号 然后选择每个单元格
then selecting each of the cells with a plus sign in between.
并在中间输入加号将这两个单元格相加
If I come back later,
在输入一些公式之后
after entering some formulas,
稍后再回来的话
I can examine a cell by selecting it and see
我可以选择该单元格并查看公式栏
the formula that's hidden inside by looking at the formula bar.
查看隐藏在其中的公式
Another handy trick is to click on
另一个实用技巧是
the formula bar which highlights all the cells that are used in the formula.
点击公式栏可以突出显示公式中用到的所有单元格
The main menu includes the most custom features of
主菜单包含了特定电子表格应用
the particular spreadsheet application and varies somewhat
最常见的自定义功能
between Google Excel, Apple Numbers etc.
并且 Google 表格、Excel、Apple Numbers 等等之间各不相同
We're going to focus on the features they have in common.That's coming up next.
接着我们将重点讲解它们的共同功能